What color is a fish? 

How big is a bird? 

How fast is a car? 

How loud is sound? 

What tempurature is hot? 

If batmans parents are dead, how was he born?

What would happen if I hired two private investigators to follow each other?

What kind of fruit is in Juicy Fruit?

Is a hotdog a sandwich?

Is cereal a soup?

How much milk is there in the Milky Way?

How dead is the dead sea?

What color is Blue from Blue’s Clues?

What color is a green house?

Will people ever walk on the sun?
const store = {
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'What color is a fish?',
      answers: [
        'Red',
        'Green',
        'Blue',
        'Gold'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Gold',
      currentA: 0,
      currentQ: true
    },
    {
      question: 'How big is a bird?',
      answers: [
        'Birds aren't real',
        'Big enough',
        '10 inches',
        '8 feet'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Big enough',
      currentA: 0,
      currentQ: false
    },
    {
      question: 'Is cereal a soup?',
      answers: [
        'Yes, obviously',
        "Yes, but to be specific it's a stew",
        "It's actually a salad. Milk is a dressing",
        'No, I like being wrong'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Yes, but to be specific it's a stew',
      currentA: 0,
      currentQ: false
    },
    {
      question: 'How much milk is there in the Milky Way?',
      answers: [
        'Technically all of it',
        'At least 3',
        '6.7 * 10^5 1km^3',
        '1 Liter'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Technically all of it',
      currentA: 0,
      currentQ: false
    },
    {
      question: 'What tempurature is the "hot potato"?',
      answers: [
        '95°C',
        'Hot',
        '0°K',
        '210°F'
      ],
      correctAnswer: '210°F',
      currentA: 0,
      currentQ: false
    },
    {
      question: 'How fast is a car?',
      answers: [
        'Faster than mine',
        '120 mph',
        'Fast?',
        'Fast AND Furious'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Fast AND Furious',
      currentA: 0,
      currentQ: false
    },
    {
      question: 'Is a hotdog a sandwich?',
      answers: [
        'No, I'm to scared to face the truth',
        'Yes, and any sandwich with a seam is, in fact, a hot dog',
        "It's closer to a wrap",
        'No, the buns surface is not perpindicular to the crust'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Yes, and any sandwich with a seam is, in fact, a hot dog',
      currentA: 0,
      currentQ: false
    },
    {
      question: 'What kind of fruit is in Juicy Fruit?',
      answers: [
        'Lemon, Orange, Pineapple and Banana',
        '"Artificial flavors"',
        'Jackfruit',
        'Juicy'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Lemon, Orange, Pineapple and Banana',
      currentA: 0,
      currentQ: false
    },
    {
      question: 'How loud is sound?',
      answers: [
        'Loud',
        '70 dB',
        'Silent',
        'Yes'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Loud',
      currentA: 0,
      currentQ: false
    },
    {
      question: 'If batmans parents are dead, how was he born?',
      answers: [
        'Magic',
        'Alfred spawned Bruce inside a test tube who was incubated by the biggest bat Alfred could find',
        'Robin laid an egg',
        'Batman never had any parents because he is, secretly, just a clone of Bruce Wayne.'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'Robin laid an egg',
      currentA: 0,
      currentQ: false
    },
    {
      question: 'How dead is the dead sea?',
      answers: [
        'Not dead',
        'Pretty dead',
        'Extremely dead',
        "So dead it doesn't exist"
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'So dead it doesn't exist',
      currentA: 0,
      currentQ: false
    },
    {
      question: "What color is Blue from Blue’s Clues?",
      answers: [
        'Blue',
        '#99dbff',
        'Blue's Clues is a lie',
        'The same color as Violet from that one scene in Willy Wonka & the Chocolate Factory'
      ],
      correctAnswer: '#99dbff',
      currentA: 0,
      currentQ: false
    },
  ],
  quizStarted: false,
  questionNumber: 0,
  score: 0
};
